You know you have the spirit of witchcraft.
Yes.
You always threaten this man with
divorce; you want to leave the house.
Yes, it always comes into my mind.
I have thoughts that I have to commit suicide, that I have to leave him,
and that I have to make him nothing.
Manifestation Of Evil Spirits
Holy Ghost!
I want to destroy her.
I want to destroy her and
I want to put his name on it.
You want to do what?
I want to make him nothing.
- You want to make him nothing?
- Yes!
Why?
Holy Ghost!
Talk!
In the name of Jesus, why do
you want to make him nothing?
He says: "Myself and my family will work for God."
Okay.
Holy Ghost, in the name of Jesus!
You say what?
To destroy him.
- You want to destroy him?
- Yes.
Why?
Because he wants to serve God.
- Because he wants to serve God?
- Yes.
- Because you hate him to serve God?
Watch your screen.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
The evil spirits in a woman speaking - that this is the wife of this man.
The evil spirit says it wants to destroy the husband.
Deliverance In Jesus' Name
If she is delivered and this man is not
delivered, we have not done anything
because she has deposited something in him.
So she is delivered and he is delivered.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
You can serve your God.
- I want to serve my God.
- You can serve GOD!
Yes! Hallelujah!
That is my only ambition: to serve my God to the last moment of my life.
Hallelujah.
Now you are free!
Go and give your husband a hug.
Set Free In Jesus' Name
Watch your screen.
Total deliverance for the husband and wife.
"What the Lord has joined" together...
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You for setting us free and delivering us, Lord!
We want to serve You, Lord!
Where there is solution,
there is forgiveness.
Where there is no solution,
there is no forgiveness.
This is solution.
Now, she is a wonderful woman.
It is the antecedent; it is biological make-up.
So now she is free, never in your life remind her again -
no matter what happens in the house.
If you people disagree,
that is the area you should not mention.
If you mention that, you offend God.
Thank you.
Thank you, Man of God!
Thank You, Jesus!
She is going to join you in the ministry.
Yes, she is going to join you.
Wonderful!
She is an evangelist.
She is going to join you in the ministry.
TESTIMONY CONTINUES
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
Yes, indeed God is with us.
My name is Mrs Rina Matthew.
Next to me is my beloved husband
Matthew Varughese.
Next to him is our beloved
daughter Marylin Matthew.
We are originally from India
but we are living in New Zealand.
The problem that brought us to
The SCOAN, Nigeria, was a marital problem.
Ever since I got married to my husband,
there was neither peace nor happiness.
There was always fighting;
there was a spirit of anger and hatred in me.
We never met together as
husband and wife in peace.
It was just a forceful sleep on
the same bed.
I was very angry and I was
having hatred within me.
But when the spirit was away from me, I used to pity myself and be very guilty about what I was doing.
But the moment the spirit came back to me,
I would be so rebellious and arrogant towards him.
When the spirit was in me, it was
like a hundred-men power within me.
I could not be controlled by anyone.
I used to smash utensils, break things, bang the doors and tear clothes.
It was like a big mess.
My husband had taken me in
India to many pastors.
They said that there was some force in me,
and they advised me to fast and pray.
I did 40 days fast, 21 days fast
and seven days fast.
They advised me to do Esther fast,
which is without water and food
for three days, and I did it but nothing happened.
I was taken for prayers but the
spirit in me never manifested.
Once I was back home from the prayer
I used to fight with my husband telling him:
"You are insulting me, taking me everywhere and saying that I have got some spirits".
It was like my husband was just in hell, I can say.
In the house, it was like in 'hell'
but when I was outside meeting people,
I was such a humble person.
No one would ever think
that I had such a behavior.
I am a nurse. At work, my
concentration started diminishing.
I was not able to concentrate on
anything I did.
After eight hours of work, I used to
run back to the hospital
to see whether my patients were alright
and the documentation that I was doing was correct.
People used to ask me why I
used to go back again to the hospital.
I would say: "Oh no, I forgot something".
And then I used to check all the documents
whether they were correct or not.
Later, because the trouble was
too much, we came to New Zealand in 2004.
Over there also, we went to many pastors,
they all said that there was some demonic attack,
but no one was able to deliver me.
When I was at work in the hospital,
my husband used to google
to find pastors who could deliver me
and restore our family.
In 2009, he found our beloved Prophet TB Joshua
on YouTube, delivering people
and that was how we came
to know about him and ever since
then we had been trying to come.
But demons know that this
is the arena of liberty
and whoever steps into it,
the demons cannot stay on that person.
So this was what brought you and your husband to The SCOAN,
and we've seen the cassette of what happened,
how you were delivered in the name of Jesus.
So tell us, what was that deliverance like,
and since then how has life been?
On the 27th of February 2011,
it was a Sunday service,
we were allowed to sit in the front line.
The moment I was given the seat,
the spirit within me was
quite unsettled and was telling me to go back.
So I told my husband, "I don't
want to sit in the front line. Shall I go back?"
But he just held my hand and said,
"No, no, no. Don't worry, we'll sit in the front".
I was a bit disturbed, I didn't want
to say something to my husband.
So the spirit in me said: "Don't worry. You have gone to so many places, you won't be located".
But thanks be to God, when the man of God just came to me all of a sudden,
the light that was flashing from the man of God -
the spirit within me could not withstand that light.
The spirit was exposed and you have seen the deliverance that has taken place in my life.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
Glory be to God!
And now since your deliverance, tell us how life has been.
What have been the changes in your attitude towards your husband, towards the ministry and so on?
Thanks be to God that I was delivered
and ever since then, I have been so light.
I slept like a baby the same night
and ever since then there is no anger and hatred.
There is love - immense love.
As our prophet has taught us that
we are the sons and daughters of love,
that same love is flowing through me.
I love my husband. Ever since then,
there was no fight,
and there is no more confusion in our lives.
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
What a wonderful testimony of
a marriage and a family restored!
Now tell us, what is your advice to people who are going through the same kind of problem -
marital problem or marital difficulty all over the world?
Before that, I would like to say that the man of God prophesied to me,
saying that I'm going to help my husband with the gospel ministry
and I'm going to be an evangelist and that prophecy is true.
God gave me an opportunity for a year to study the Bible,
and I am sharing the Word to many people.
Now, I've gone back to my profession as a nurse,
working in NICU - that is neonatal
premature babies in ICU.
I apply the Anointing Water every day before I go to work.
I pray with my husband and I take the sticker with me.
I put it inside my uniform and whenever I touch the babies, there will be miracles taking place.
Babies are getting healed before the doctors discharge them from the hospital.
Thank You, Jesus!
Thank You for setting us free and delivering us, Lord.
We want to serve You, Lord.
Where there is solution, there is forgiveness.
Where there is no solution, there is no forgiveness.
This is solution.
Now, she is a wonderful woman.
It is the antecedent; it is biological make-up.
So now she is free, never in your life remind her again, no matter what happens in the house.
If you people disagree, that is
an area you should not mention.
If you mention that, you offend God.
Thank you.
Thank you, Man of God!
Thank You, Jesus!
She is going to join you in the ministry.
Yes, she is going to join you. Wonderful!
She is an evangelist.
She is going to join you in the ministry.
Testimony Time
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
Put your hands together for Jesus, the Miracle Worker!
To the whole world, I would like to say especially to my Indian brothers and sisters back in our country,
it has been taught that being a Christian, demons cannot possess you or attack you.
That is a wrong teaching, my brothers and sisters.
Wherever in the family there is trouble, fight, disagreement, anger, alcoholism and smoking,
it means that you are possessed with demons.
Demons have invaded your
family and you need to be delivered.
Come to this place, The SCOAN, Nigeria.
You can spend whatever you have to get yourself delivered,
to restore your family and everything
shall be added unto you.
Hallelujah! Let's put our hands
together for Jesus once again!
As we know, The SCOAN is just one of the many living churches all over the world.
And what our mother is advising
us is that we must receive deliverance
to become a Christian or a truly born-again person.
You can receive deliverance in any living church
where the Holy Spirit is in charge all over the world.
Glory be to God! We thank God for your testimony.
We would love to hear a word from your husband now.
Sir, you are very welcome.
Please introduce yourself and share
your wonderful testimony with us.
I'm Matthew Varughese,
and my wife Rina Matthew and
my daughter Marylin Matthew.
The prophetic message that
was given during our deliverance,
especially for me to serve God,
and all this drama was taking place
because of my urge for serving God.
As the man of God says, faith attracts testing, and I was enduring for so many years.
We got married to have a good family life but I have seen hell on this earth.
But God helped me to stand; I only looked to Jesus Christ, who took everything on Himself.
Every day, I used to pray and read the Bible,
and that endurance made me to stand my ground.
Now the thing is that after that prophetic word,
he said that I should go and serve my GOD!
That opened a breakthrough for me
and after that, I have been used by God to pray for others
and a lot of breakthroughs have come.
God is using us nicely and I have really been strong enough now.
I need more grace but then I am strong enough.
God is helping me to do His work,
and I'm happy with my family.
My wife understands me now; challenges come but we understand each other
and she is now able to assist me
in many things.
Glory be to God. So the prophecy
of the man of God has exactly come true.
You have been able to serve the
Lord in spirit and in truth.
Your ministry has had a breakthrough and your wife is assisting you in her role as an evangelist.
Is that right?
Yes, thank you.
Glory be to God. And what can you say about your wife's character towards you as her husband
and her character as a wife since the deliverance and the word of prophecy?
After the deliverance she takes care,
we sit and discuss so many things, we minister to people together,
and whenever people call us, we are able to pray together, before we pray for others.
Most of the situations are like what
we have gone through in our life -
those problems are coming
so it is very easy to understand.
And as the man of God says that
every cause has got a purpose
and that is really becoming true in our life,
and we are going through that.
Hallelujah! Let's put our
hands together for Jesus!
Pastor, we can see your daughter
standing next to you here.
Can you tell us - what changes have you seen between your wife and your daughter
since the deliverance took place?
Before the deliverance, the problem
was that she was not taken care of.
She felt always lonely because she is the only child
who was born to us after seven years of marriage.
So she was lonely. She was not been taken care of.
But now after the deliverance, she and her mother are able to give more time to each other,
and they are having a better understanding
and we are all happy together.
Hallelujah. So finally, pastor, give us your word of advice to people watching all over the world -
both to pastors and to married couples who should seek the face of the Lord.
I would like to say, Jesus Christ
is the God whose ministry is restoration.
As at the marriage of Cana,
the water was turned to wine,
when a family had the
problem of being short of wine.
And then Jesus was there. When we call upon Jesus Christ, He will make a way for us.
So never ever quit, stay in faith, call upon God;
ask, seek, and knock.
And definitely God will make a way for you
and He will deliver you.
Let's put our hands together
for Jesus Christ!
My name is Marilyn Matthew.
I'm from New Zealand.
This is my mother Rina Matthew,
and that is my father Matthew Varughese.
In 2012, I came to The SCOAN.
The man of God prophesied that the same spirit
that was haunting my mother was also haunting me.
I can testify to that. Yes, it was haunting me
because there were so many things that I did.
I felt anger and frustration
that I never used to feel before.
After the man of God prophesied to me,
I got delivered.
I was set free. After that, there is
happiness and peace in our family.
Hallelujah. So what would be your word of advice
to families watching you all over the world?
I would like to give advice to children because sometimes, when your parents are fighting
or your family is going through a bad situation, children are mostly affected.
And I want to tell them to hold on to Jesus, to pray to Jesus.
He will surely hear your prayers.
Hallelujah. Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
Wonderful! You have demonstrated and you have experienced
that earth has no sorrow that Heaven does not feel.
When God Almighty is aware of your situation, He will not leave you without a solution.
And as God has met you at the point of your need
and is taking you from grace
to grace and faith to faith,
we pray God Almighty will give you that grace to remain in His Word,
abide in His Word and allow the Word to abide in you
that this will be permanent, in Jesus' name.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
We believe you have been inspired
by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing lives, Changing nations and Changing the world.
RV: PavelTatyanaZheleznyakov